{
    "id": "0ad3afcdca8040d5a07750433708928e",
    "title": "Conjunctions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "……………………… we reached the place, it was quite dark.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "When",
                "Though",
                "If"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………….. I had never seen him before, I went ahead and introduced myself.",
            "description": "Though is used to connect two contrasting ideas.",
            "answers": [
                "Though",
                "When",
                "If"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "………………………….. she earns a lot of money, she spends hardly anything.",
            "description": "Though is used to connect two contrasting ideas.",
            "answers": [
                "Though",
                "Because",
                "If"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "………………………….. they are poor, they cannot afford even the basic necessities of life.",
            "description": "Because gives the reason. ",
            "answers": [
                "Though",
                "Because",
                "If"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The phone rang ……………………………… I was having a nap in the afternoon.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "when",
                "if",
                "because"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………….. you put in your best efforts, you are bound to succeed.",
            "description": "If expresses a condition. ",
            "answers": [
                "If",
                "Though"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "………………………….. I had warned him, he didn’t pay heed to me.",
            "description": "Though is used to connect two contrasting ideas. ",
            "answers": [
                "If",
                "Because",
                "Though"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "………………………….. you wait long enough, you will get what you want.",
            "description": "If expresses a condition. ",
            "answers": [
                "Because",
                "If",
                "Though"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "………………………….. he has a good job, he is not satisfied.",
            "description": "Though is used to connect two contrasting ideas.",
            "answers": [
                "Though",
                "Because",
                "If"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "She was upset ……………………………. she couldn’t get the job.",
            "description": "Because gives the reason.",
            "answers": [
                "if",
                "because",
                "when"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………….. I reached the station, the train had already left.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "If",
                "When",
                "Though"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………………. it was raining, we went jogging.",
            "description": "Though is used to connect two contrasting ideas.",
            "answers": [
                "Though",
                "Because",
                "If"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}